My brain is mush. Jaemyun. Go away.
I need to study.
So, how to say fighting in English?
Just good luck. Good luck?
Yeah. Okay. Good luck. Thank you. Bye.
So when I went to university, I studied international studies
and had minors in German business and nonprofit administration.
None of it had to do with education.
I never knew I wanted to go into education at the time.
Now that I'm trying to get into the Teaching Credential Program,
they looked at my transcript from University of Oregon
and just unfortunately not enough of my class is transferred to be like to suit their requirements to get into the credential program.
So because of that, I have to take what is called the CSET test.
And that is actually three different tests.
And each test has multiple subjects that it covers.
So the first one that I took yesterday was the English and History test.
So all of that is just as part of the application process for the credential program.
I'm also taking prerequisite classes.
I was lucky enough to get two classes waived based on my experience teaching in Korea.
And then also because to get the job in Korea,
I had to take a TEFL class to get TEFL certified.
um which is teaching english as a foreign language
um so those were able to cover two of my classes but i still have to take two more
that again is just for the teaching credential program which is through a university here
um i will have to take
i'll have to student teach for a year
and then i will have to take classes as well for the year before i can then get certified,
and start working in a classroom.
So yesterday I took the first subtest, English and History,
but it was hard. It was a lot of content to study for,
so you obviously don't know when it's such a wide range of content.
You kind of pick and choose what you think are the most likely to come up on the test,
but you never know what you're going to get.
So multiple choice. That was pretty much how I thought it was going to be.
It did cover, I think, areas that I didn't study as much.
And I have, when I took practice tests, I did well in.
But always when it comes to the actual test, the pressure of that test, I feel like I secondguess myself a lot.
So it's really hard to say how I did.
When it came to
The constructed responses,
which are like short answer,
ones that you have to write,
I felt like three of them were kind of what I was expecting, and I think I did decently.
I don't know if I'll get, like, the highest score is out of the three.
I don't know if I'll get a three on any of them.
It would be nice to at least get it on one, maybe two.
But I think it's more likely I'll get twos out of them.
I think I did enough for twos.
But there was one for the history portion.
It was a topic I was not expecting.
for a short answer one.
So that one I was not prepared for
and that one... I was really having to just kind of... come up with something
and I don't know if I can curse but to just basically bullshit my way through
because I had no idea so I was just kind of making stuff up
kind of hoping that it would work um
so I think I'll be lucky if I get one point for that one
Working in Korea. definitely opened my eyes to how much I like to work with kids and teach.
And it's something I enjoy doing.
I don't know how to like,
I don't have this indepth answer of why I want to teach
like it is something I kind of fell into and found that I just actually really enjoyed it.
And I want to keep doing it.